Your attention is scarce, but every day feeds, taps, and algorithms decide what gets it.
What if you could take that control back?
You already have the signal, your calendar, talks, messages, projects, watchlists, and
the assistants connected to them.
But most of it still comes back as more text.
And before the day even starts, nobody wants another wall of text.
Streamed text changes the format.
Inside the Codex app, it turns your trusted sources into a short personalized video briefing
you can actually watch, not what the algorithms want to push.
What you need to know.
Here is a new style explainer on the NPM Supply Chain attack built from trusted sources, ranked
for relevance, and delivered as a concise video.
More engaging than a summary, faster to absorb than a wall of text.
But this is bigger than news video.
Streamed text can create a daily plan, a project recap, a news digest, an architecture update,
a team handoff, or a recap from the tools you have connected.
If you can connect the tools, you can build the stream.
And because streamed text runs inside the Codex app, you can schedule automations to
generate these briefings before your day starts.
So on a metro ride, you can watch what is planned for the day, what changed overnight,
and what your other automations already finished for you.
Instead of opening 5 apps and reading 5 summaries, you can get one briefing in a format built
for attention.
Your sources, your ranking, your format, your stream.
Streamed text.
Watch your signal, not the algorithm.